Hammond, Reese Papers 5954
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Reese Hammond Papers
1977-1993
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Hammond, Reese
5954
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
5743712
Biographical / Historical
Mr. Hammond was a member of the Advisory Panel for the Dictionary of Occupational Titles.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives 227 Ives Hall Tower Road Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheelref@cornell.edu https://catherwood.library.cornell.edu/kheel/
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 16, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 18, 2019
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5974: Reese Hammond Additional Papers
Hammond, Reese; Advisory Panel for the Dictionary of Occupational Titles (U.S.)
5743712
- Reese Hammond (Box 1, Folder 1)
- The Changing World of Work: Implications for the DOT Review Initiative, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  Spiral Book - April 5, 1991
- Classification of Instructional Programs, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- ADPOT Meeting, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  June 6-7, 1991
- Fort Worth: Project C3 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- DOT Review: An Assessment of User Needs & Collection/Classification Methods, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Spiral Book - May 10, 1991
- APDOT Subcommittee Meetings, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  April 29-30, 1992
- APDOT Meeting, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  September 24-25, 1992
- APDOT Meeting, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  December 15, 1992
- APDOT Meeting, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  September 25-27, 1991
- Georgia State University, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Use of the DOT, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Career Information Delivery Systems, August 1991
- National Career Development Association, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Reese Hammond Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- APDOT Drafts, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- National Occupational Classification, 1986-1990 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Reese to Sidney, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- The New DOT: A Database of Occupational Titles for the Twenty-First Century, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  March 22, 1993
- DOT User Survey: A Report & Analysis, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  February 1993
- ADPOT Meeting, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  January 15, 1992
- Fort Worth: Project C3 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- APDOT, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  January 13-14, 1992
- Leadership Effectiveness Survey, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  October 1991
- Miscellaneous, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- The New DOT: A Database of Occupational Titles for the Twenty-First Century, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Dictionary of Occupational Titles, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Book
- Marilyn Silver to Reese Hammond Papers, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Revising DOT, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Collection, Publication & Dissemination of DOT Data, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Spiral Book - August 1992
- Dictionary of Occupational Titles Volume I, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Dictionary of Occupational Titles Volume II, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Dictionary of Occupational Titles, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- DOT Survey & Research Service Project, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- National Occupational Classification, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Book - March 1990
- Canadian Occupational Analysis System, 1987-1991 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Draft Research Design Report, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  Spiral Book - November 16, 1990
- ADPOT Meeting, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  January 14-15, 1991
- ADPOT, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- ADPOT Meeting, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  October 24-25, 1990
- Miscellaneous, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 16)